good morning it is our
last friday of possibility during the
pandemic
and today we are doing the fourth
or fifth and final uh coaching session
so this one we are doing today is the
brain walk
the kit
is in the description on youtube and it
has this worksheet in it
as well as a brain map that has some
letters and numbers on it which i don't
know here it's the
brain walk but it has four letters
during it
it's my favorite of the brain walks um
you get a lot of information
and i actually think because you get so
much information and then you can pick
and choose
what to decode that it's actually really
helpful
so to get started we're just going to do
the very brief
activity if i can refine the paper so i
don't butcher it like two
like two weeks ago the center of the
earth activity
there we go all right
ah take a deep breath i like this one
better
center of the earth with your eyes open
or closed i invite you to take a couple
of deep breaths from your diaphragm
with your feet flat on the floor imagine
the sun is in the center of this planet
allow the warmth from the sun to enter
your feet
and slowly move up from your toes to the
top of your head
enjoy the relaxed feeling when you are
ready
we can begin coaching
and so taking this we usually come up
with a goal
at the beginning and then sometimes you
have to switch into a question this one
i know
starts as a question so i'm just going
to start with a question
and my question i have that i'm asking
myself today
i don't even know what it is yet
how do i best move forward
with this new conversation for
conversations
i'd best okay no that's not seeming like
the right question
like you already answered that
how to find
people for
process raising
that's how to communicate it or where to
find them
how to find people for process raising
which out of the four questions that we
will be starting not next week where i'm
taking off but the week after
the solution raising which we already
got going on i don't have a problem with
that one
the process raising talking about how
can we actually create a process with
ten thousand people and a hundred
thousand dollars
so that ten 000 people can create a
project with a hundred thousand dollars
and that is who i'm looking for that
group of people and so that's what i'm
talking about the other two
conversations on top of that are one
that's about the dance and i want it
specifically for game b people
it's kind of like the spirituality and
actually so it's weird that i'm focusing
on this one when both the
spirituality one or the five questions
and the dance
i also want people to have a
conversation with and i don't know how
to phrase that one either
and the um communications one so
actually how to find people for
the how to find
the right people for the conversations
yes okay so
there's a deck of cards that has the
values on it but since i can't really
put a deck of cards
in the in the kit i'm gonna do what
everyone else can do as well
if you can find it from organizing me
which is the values chart
if you pick i can't even pull this a
camera if it
find up to seven that jump off the page
at you whether that's just them jumping
off the page when you're reading them or
you can close your eyes and feel them
and open your eyes and pick them
oh i love it love it well they can find
the paper and a pen
all at the same time there we go
okay my first one is beauty
which is a theme in my life i can
explain that later
compassion
and as always i'm writing these out of
order because of the way that it's
written on there i write all the odds
and then the
detachment
get some good ones this morning
enthusiasm or was that faith
somehow both okay
and let's get one from this final column
oh that's blank we went past it
that's a good one right there
oh reverence
and one from this middle column
obedience my favorite yay
okay i guess i should be reading the
actual
brainwalk solutions and i'm just doing
it okay
take a brain walk okay
when you think about a question
something that you need solutions to
invite you to think about your real
issue or goal which is
if we've done that part there's another
person
and think of a question for which you
need solutions it may be
simply be your real goal put into a
question or it could be a question
related to a specific aspect of your
real goal
the question should begin with how or
what and should be as specific as
possible
example how can i create how can i
better communicate with my boss
or what can i do to improve my sales
record this question at the top of your
worksheet let me know
what it is let me know what it is in the
comment section i guess
and so i'm just making sure mine is that
how can i find the right people
for the conversations yeah that feels
you know i mean because it's like all
four conversations how to find the right
people
i know whoever shows up is the right
people so basically just a number of
people
all right you read your question briefly
and shuffle this cli values card we did
that differently
we'll be using these values at the end
of the session within these values there
may be answers to your question
now we are ready to begin the walk which
means you need the brain mark
itself and i can't hold it up so you do
need it in the thing because you're
gonna
follow it through and then stop on each
individual one and write down what i
tell you to write down i can't even
follow this at the mirror
good times
as you were walking please remember to
walk on the lines and keep focusing on
your question
imagine yourself walking through the
left right conscious subconscious and
super conscious parts of your mind in
search of solutions
using the middle finger of the hand you
naturally write with begin the walk by
pushing the marker
on the line as images words feelings
ideas sounds come to you
stop the marker and record them in stage
two
i should probably have a marker for this
oh look there's a dime right here
okay so i'm starting on the start part
middle
middle finger of my right hand you're
welcome
the conversations i'm the right people
to have the powerful conversations we
need
to create a world that works for
everyone
how do you do that
so now i got to the a and
i'm gonna stop and record
okay animal like
up
all right it jumps ahead all right
i'm just going by just animal move to
human now i'm moving to
plant
and mineral
why is it always that i don't believe
you have stoned of any minerals
that's quite impossibility oh actually
changed
interesting i'll keep that one there
okay
now in the center
all right private h
so i'll read this for anyone else closer
so when you get to the a
a represents animal an animal a bird a
foul a mammal or reptile
close your eyes and allow your intuitive
brain to give you the name of an animal
continue walking until you arrive at the
h which represents human
people person race spirit angel
etc close your eyes and allow your
intuitive brain to give you the name of
a human being
then continue walking until you arrive
at the p
which represents a plant tree bush
flower grass herb crop etc
close your eyes eyes and allow your
intuitive brain to give you the name of
a plant
let me know what you get
continue walking until you arrive at m
which represents mineral
rock gem whole iron etc
close your eyes and allow your intuitive
brain to give you a name of a mineral or
rock
then you continue on the walk to the
pink center this represents your heart
space
close your eyes and allow yourself to be
truly in your heart about your question
let me know what you get you can open
your eyes
to allow this information i'm just fine
about you to walk back
so now we're going to walk back out of
the map
with the middle finger of the opposite
hand
i don't know if they get things with us
but
all right now we get to decoding
i believe let's get out of ourselves
here decoding
we are now ready to decode this decoding
process will allow you to turn your
images words
etc which have sprung from the highest
creative centers in your brain into
solutions to your question
my question don't know what your
question is sharing it in my comments
but my question is how can i find the
right people
for the conversations
and i didn't get anything walking in
i have my values which are beauty
compassion detachment enthusiasm
faith reverence and obedience
really hope that's reverence i can't
actually read my writing
um and then i didn't get anything else
walking in the
animal i got was a monkey hanging in a
tree by its tail
the human was einstein this crazy hair
like an old einstein the picture that's
normally
normally seen of him uh the plant i got
it was plantain which i didn't know what
it was a few years ago but it grows here
it's a medicinal
native plants to to this region and
once i saw it once i learned what it was
i see it everywhere and it grows in the
cracks and it grows
in and so i think that's the piece of it
it's like the
anyway the mineral i first got was
copper and i get copper a lot so that my
braid was like fine
and it gave me salt so we'll see how
that goes
uh my heart space in the center
i got a bridge and more specifically
this bridge in vancouver the lions gate
bridge
that going over the bridge from stanley
park like that specific windy right
before you get on the bridge the fact
that the bridge is really
old but very necessary necessary at the
moment
is there's something there okay so now
you take what you got in the walk
and you put it over into here but not
just the name so
refer to my question how do i find the
people for the conversation
the animal that i got is a monkey
so what power words come to mind when i
think of a monkey
and
playful mischievous they're powerful
but also um community
that almost all primate species are in
groups and that is also part of their
power it's like their intelligence their
playfulness
mischievousness all brought into one as
well as the fact that they're in groups
the feelings uh monkey
it was weirdly disappointment when i
first got it it's like i'll be a monkey
like not even a chimpanzee or a gorilla
it's like the lower of the privates well
but it has a tail so that's okay
it's like oh that's because i usually
get an elephant i almost always get
nothing but i got an elephant
walking back on the way out and an
evergreen which are two common symbols
that i get the feelings i get let's read
this because i don't think it's okay
when you think of this animal what is
the most powerful word that comes to
mind
in a playful mischievous community what
feeling does this animal invoke for you
playfulness
how are these feelings and power do we
go on to this how do these feelings and
power words suggest a logical solution
to my question
so how can i find the people how can i
find the right people for my
conversation
and i think that's keep it light
and fun don't start
every half of the world's bad day no you
need to
you don't know you don't want to come
have a conversation with me why why
like keeping it playful and fun that
like the point is to have fun during the
conversation
yeah okay einstein
when you think of this human what's the
most powerful word that comes to mind
in stage three of your work you write
down this word it's funny because it was
of course intelligence it's einstein and
the second one was compassion
and it was it was of course
intelligence and then compassion was
actually like the bigger one
okay which is interesting
bigger bigger bigger okay what feelings
does this human evoke for you
pride is the wrong word but
i can't think of what the word is not
envious of
in awe of i look up to einstein i think
einstein was a good human being
it was also intelligence intelligence
intelligent
and so feelings
as much as i get it like celebrity
status
like wanting to be like
how does that suggest a
power word suggestion solution to your
question
okay which is what i was already doing i
love when it's already once
like wasn't i already doing that why is
this just continuing what we're doing
which is as well as the conversation
being fun
that people bring their own intelligence
and with compassion thrown in
i'm very much able to see that everybody
is intelligent
i don't besides when i get into lower
states
that anyone is stupid anyone is is
less than another um including if they
actually have less of an iq or whatever
other way you want to measure
whatever intelligence you're measuring
but it's letting people show up and be
themselves
and truly so it's like intelligence
means compassion
bring your own intelligence to it i
don't know how to communicate with that
though
the whole time but thank you
subconscious
ways to be like
okay so
bring
it's like it is an intellectual
conversation and yet i don't actually
want to frame it in that way because i
don't want
those people showing up i want people
who want to have a conversation about
compassion about technology about
them i get it
okay fire bring your intelligence
but like okay
that's what well writing out whatever it
was i just got
changed into bring your intelligence but
more importantly bring your heart to
like the people coming to the
conversation
i already assume you're an intelligent
person just all the fact you have
experience you're gonna bring that
with you but having
like how to invite compassion for the
other people
so that we can all all express the
intellect there's something here okay
so the plant now we're on to the plant
the plant i recorded in stage two is the
salt
no it's plantain there we go that's a
plant
when you think of this plant what is the
most powerful word that comes to mind
resilient healing
and awareness or feelings that come to
mind okay that one is awareness
versatility
how does plantain how do these feelings
and this power word suggest solutions to
my question how do i find the right
people for the
conversations and
i love it because that same thing i said
at the beginning about plantain where i
didn't know what it was and then once i
knew what it was it was everywhere
it is truly everywhere um
and then it enters your your conscious
once it's in your conscious you see it
much more clearly and there's something
about that
like i already know all of the people
who are going to be part of these
conversations
they just need to be aware i want to do
this in which case they will like come
through the cracks
they will there are cracks they'll come
they'll come
okay
already know me it's about me not being
aware of them versus them not existing
right the plantain existed the whole
time
it was my unawareness of it made me not
registered in my conscious mind
the same thing of course everyone's
intelligent every not everyone is going
to be playful and what
but that three like intelligence but i
give everyone intelligence so as long as
you're okay showing up and getting it
wrong sometimes for your ego
then the intelligence piece solves it
like i don't
i don't care that you have a degree i
don't care if your iq is high i don't
care if you can string your sentence
together
and hopefully some amount of coherence
will figure it out fair though but
um the compassionate piece to want
others to succeed to want to help others
even when we come up against our
emotions
that caring piece is very big and then
the third piece
was it the fun that they want and
again it naturally happens that um
like if you invoke fun and make it like
it's
gonna be fun it's not and whereas if you
allow it to emerge
then the dance and the people that are
there
and the playfulness that emerges makes
it it's i don't
yeah anyway okay the mineral
the mineral i got was salt
it was salt after copper which again i
get all the time
it turns green i don't know what copper
is but salt
is oh what is the power word for salt
it's weird
because salt is power and money
previously
um if you're the person who owns the
salt line not the person working in it
of course
but that it was prestige and power and
money
and yet now due to its abundance
it isn't in fact we're trying to get
less of it instead of more of it right
in our
in our diets that see too much of it too
little of it you die
too much of it it's about balance and so
balance is the
and shifting like the shifting history
that salt used to be so integral to
society
um and yet it was always plentiful it
was always
in our ocean water it was always there
but it wasn't
you don't have the knowledge on how to
get it and so how do you like it's
supply and demand like it's it's weird
supply and demand stuff balance
okay so how is this a powered suggestion
for your question
find the balance finding the balance and
that also means
okay gotcha
all right so now i've decoded
cody is there another page to this
because it seems that i'm missing a page
all right heartbreak oh yeah yeah what
did i get
uh the lions gate bridge stanley park i
forgot about that one what am i
representing for that hard space oh i
see i did this wrong
thoughts ideas and solutions what does
lionsgate bridge be again
historically it was hard to do but we
did it
whereas now it would somewhat be easier
and safer to create one but we don't go
around creating bridges all the time
um in fact both the second arrows and
landscape range are really old
and there's something in about and the
fact that
like this lionsgate bridge is both this
like
beautiful oh okay um
it is like one of the most gorgeous
places in vancouver to me
this winding path in stanley park
you're in a car if i'm in a bus i really
enjoy it
it has um an emotional
impact that bridge because i saw someone
jump off at one at one point
and every time i'm there i'm reminded of
that but you know we're like oh yeah
that happened
and i was crossing this at one point in
time and
the fact that it's like this beautiful
place
that's also old that we don't really
make anymore but it's also
i can't even think what the word is like
a checkpoint like a
throttling of traffic
what is that called like a congestion
point like all of vancouver getting over
the north shore and vice versa and they
have to switch and every day it's a
show because of
the the amount of like our population
hasn't kept up with the needs of the
bridge and yet everyone's using it right
like it doesn't make sense we need
another one
and it's beautiful and it's it's like
it's
this entryway though this congestion
that it doesn't matter to 7.5 billion
people it's like
this is the is the conversation and
every conversation is like that
and it's not about it's about finding
that threshold of people and i know that
but there's something about that
entryway archway that is
like people coming together going
through it and then
dispersing
i don't even know quite what it is but
like there's something about that
all right oh
now ask us to think about three action
steps you can take as a result of our
work today to answer this question look
at the solutions you have recorded in
stages
two three as well as your stage three to
coding information
these action steps will answer the
question at the top of the worksheet
what do you think or three actions could
be kindly turn them into smart goals
yeah i can do that
so
what do i do one of the things was very
simply
in my mind all four conversations
somewhat have to start next week i'm
taking off
and starting the week after solution
racing is happy next week and it will be
continuing to happen
and so really next week's solution
raising is my focus
i don't even know what we're doing
solution ranging on but doing that
and then which of the other three
conversations
do i want to have most i mean the truth
is
although i want a conversation
to ex all of the conversations to take
place live online people can witness
that these
type of conversations are happening and
hopefully feel
invited to either come be part of ours
if there's room or
you start their own that
what's the playing that unless i tried
that even though
oh that i already have that one the
dance one is my omega group on
wednesdays we very much it's
where this idea keeps arising it's where
the people who happen to show up there
all have this
thing somewhat weaving in out of their
lives but there's something about
so anyway writing out
writing about
the dance and five questions
so it's not even about like i already
anyway adding
yep add one
conversation
the following week
so i don't need to add the technology
one the
dance solution raising and keep keep
solutions and add process raising
i just need to add one to the week next
and i can add another one to the week
after that so in four weeks i'll have
all
four conversations
add one conversation to the following
week
right because it's only kind of also my
other two conversations on friday and
saturday
so i will have six conversations plus
the wednesday one
seven conversations a week if i keep the
idea cafe
eight i guess we're not keeping the idea
campaign it's too much too much
what is chiming at me
interesting i don't know why i need to
check this right now
but the universe came between right now
okay so one more actionable step is
add one conversation to the following
week and then
which would be about picking the
conversation but i think what i want to
write down
is the dance and the five questions that
is more
okay writing
what the purpose what i want to get out
of as an individual and as a group
and a society
oh interesting so keep in mind have fun
kids verse 5 do this
and anyway so i'm going to be writing
what what the purpose end point of each
of these four conversations is what i
want to get out of it what i want the
group to get out of it
what i hope if enough people weren't
participating that's what society would
get out of it
and um and then from there i can kind of
write the more overarching is what i'm
looking for
but that's more for me than picking
one of those conversations that isn't
the solution raising
so that um to figure out what to start
the next week and partly it's just
putting it out to
the game b community to see which one
resonates with the most people
is it the um the dance one
the conversation the religion that's not
a religion the blue that's not a woo
the thing that weaves itself and it self
organizes life and just getting together
and talking about that in our own lives
and our
understanding of it the conversation
about
technology and the power of technology
and everything that we need to have in
place
in order for us to be able to rely
somewhat on technology to be our central
focus instead of governments
but i don't i don't want to frame it too
rigidly right those are my ideas and so
figuring out how to bring in the people
who have the big ideas about technology
who want to create it together just to
have a conversation about that
what does that look like what topics
what does the conversation
itself or the hour look like and then
how to for all of these it's also how to
make it
easy the people can find the link and
remember that it's happening and come
to it happening without me having to
start a different facebook group for all
four different conversations
it's already hard not having solution
crazy which is literally just just me
posting me like there's a solution crazy
forever wants to come and very
people show up that way anyway and so
yeah okay looking back at the values you
recorded
apply to the real goal they all applied
real cool what are you talking about
um looking back at the values that i
recorded
list three ways in which these values
provide additional solutions to my
question
so we have this order that this is in
whatever i didn't make it
beauty is hilarious because it's
something that showed up in landmark for
me and something that i am here to
create but in weird ways because i'm not
super focused on it it's a weird it's
like not aesthetic
it's like an inner beauty and i can't
because
me included it whatever beauty is weird
it's proved like when i see it reflected
in other people it's actually mine
that was at landmark there was this
point where coming up with the
basically the power words that associate
with people and
every time someone qualified be like
power and beauty power beauty power and
beauty
i have a couple other traits but like
power and beauty was
resonating with all of them and that's
because that was mine it's like oh i'm
here
for power of beauty gotcha interesting
because i wouldn't consider myself
somebody who's here to focus on beauty
but i am and as she just came into the
kitchen
my kids also very focused on it in a
very real way and i gave birth to her
this is before all that happens
i didn't let mark learn before my kid
was in existence in this life
anyway beauty compassion is what i'm
here for
it's i was born with a over abundance of
compassion
um and detachment that is the one that
i've had to learn
is a loving detachment from the
compassion
that it's not my job that struggle is
also the purpose everyone else is also
going through their
coaster and although they're not
enjoying the ride he said even though
they're on a roller coaster
um there's
there's just like the more i deeply care
about humanity but don't give a
what it thinks about me the stronger i
can step into my power and my purpose
and there's a
very strongly compassion that i already
had but also needing to learn detachment
for my own safety and own health and own
power to move it forward
um and detachment even from this right
that i don't if i'm attached
that this is the thing and people need
to show up and i get crickets it's gonna
be hard
um although i'm used to it pretty used
to it that um
instead it's detachment from the results
my job is just to do these action items
and get what i get
it's not about who shows up is who shows
up
and and it's like the play you know i
don't go outside and get mad at the
crack in the
sidewalk it doesn't have the plantain in
it
but it didn't grow here yeah because it
didn't it just didn't
and so
so you detachment enthusiasm letting it
happen when it
happens i can't force it well there's
something about doing these coaching
from the very beginning where i can feel
myself like switching over
into that space of who i am when i coach
someone
that is a very powerful place to be
where it is the sense of like
wisdom and detachment that isn't my ego
and he deadlines
and in in there like there's something
about that that i'm like oh if i
actually can tap into this i don't even
consciously do it it just
is what happens when i'm doing this it
happens much more easily when i'm
coaching somebody else than myself but
like there was that piece of that that i
could feel and tap into
and so just allowing that
detachment enthusiasm faith is weird
because when i used to get that one i'd
get offended because it was like
faith i'm so not faith i'm logical and
the irony is
i do have an immense faith that
everything's unfolding
as it's meant to and it keeps proving
itself to me so it keeps being
more a more entrenched viewpoint
and so having faith in that is my
mission
that everything is unfolding in its
right time means i can't do anything
wrong and it's going to just happen and
so
like just following my piece of it is
what i need to do
and the more i have faith in the thing i
have faith in
is and truly realize where i'm not and
why i'm not
then it's getting stronger reverence
same thing just i
mean i don't even know like reverence
really that's like
just finding the beauty and allowing the
gratitude in the moment
allowing this absurdity that we get to
create a better world and that i get to
be part of it and i like all of it
and the reverence for that obedience
really obedience it's what i'm here to
learn in some way i can't learn
obedience from authority
even obedience for myself is hard and i
need the world to be a certain way
but obedience to my inner intuition and
my guides
the quicker and more i'm obedient to
them the faster this whole thing goes
and yet i can't do it wrong and
therefore if i'm being disobedient
i'm not being disobedient if i'm being
argumentative
and stubborn then it happens slower but
it's still gonna happen
it's still gonna unfold at its right
time because when i turn down something
of being
and i'm being disobedient i'm actually
still in obedience to the dance
because there's a reason i said no and
i'm not at yes yet
and so it'll keep coming back until i
say yes or life will keep changing until
i say yes
and but that the fact that obedience
came up when it's very much a thing that
i struggle with and something that i'm
learning is amazing okay so this was the
final
friday of life coaching i remember which
one we started with i think i started
with one of the ptst tools
yeah and um and then we did one on
which one did we start with i'm pretty
sure we started with relationship with
self
and then no i just relationship with
others first i think i did my sister one
first so relationship with others we did
relationship with self
our life and period purpose was last
week this week is brainwashed solutions
although none of them i'd be like that
was stuller you should rewatch that
constantly
that the fact that i'm coaching myself
in it and the uh
kits are made available in the
descriptions you can follow along and do
it it is a powerful way to get in touch
with your subconscious
and find out how it's guiding you
because it gives the perfect
perfect advice every time and i'm
constantly astounded and i like this one
because it gives a lot of advice there's
a lot
and so not everything needs to if if
you're like monkey whatever i don't need
i don't need to decode that or what
what's with the plantain or the salt
but each of them gave a piece of it and
it's the combination for me
that gives the solution tomorrow i am
back
with 20 minutes i'll be answering the
five questions for myself for that week
before i attend the round table at 9 a.m
sunday is the last day i'm still
figuring out what i'm going to do for a
story session i might do
a future story session where like i'm
coming back from 10 years in the future
and when we've created the global tech
cooperative
and created game b and how did we get
there
right so telling the story
of the la the next 10 years as if they
already happened
and so that is what i'm currently
focused on that'll be our last
possibility in pandemic i'll be taking
next week off beside solution racing and
returning the following week
with one extra conversation that's aside
from solutions whether that's process
raising whether that's the dance
and the magic that unfolds in life and
answering the five questions
or the power of technology and how we
can use it to create the world that
works for us
as individuals and collectively i don't
know i don't know which conversation or
whether it's gonna be the solution
raising on how do we create a process
for process raising how do we create a
process to create something with ten
thousand people
who put in ten dollars we have a hundred
thousand dollars how or is there another
way to fund it to find the hundred
thousand dollars
but with all of that that is what is
coming up thank you for hanging out
those that popped in today
and someone got something out of it